The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.

**JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.** For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.

**Currency**

**USD**

**Language**

**Global**

Categories

**Search**

Search

Search

[](javascript:void(0);)

* **Privacy and Cookie Policy**

Privacy and Cookie Policy
=========================

Privacy Protection Policy of Thermaltake Technology Co. Ltd.
============================================================

Thermaltake Technology Co. Ltd. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (hereinafter as “Thermaltake” or “We”) value our members’ privacy and follow regulations like the Personal Data Protection Act, EU GDPR, etc. Therefore, we have established the Privacy Protection Policy to protect your rights and interests. Please read the following contents of the privacy protection policies carefully before you provide your personal data.

Scope of this Policy Applies
----------------------------

* This Policy applies to the relationship between you and the Website operating organization to regulate the following items related to the collecting, dealing with and use of your personal data: (1) when you have business contacts with us, or participate in every activity that we hold (including but not limited to registry as a Website member, online shopping or participate in every kind of promotion activities like, lucky draw or gifting); or (2) you use our consulting services through telephone, fax or our Web platform for inquiries or recommendations; or (3) any other Website, services or products that show our declarations, has been linked to the declaration.
    
* Any activities regarding personal data protection that by using our Website to link to any Website that a third party managed or operated shall follow the privacy policy of the third party’s or the Website. We will not be responsible for any activities of the third party’s Website.

Safety for Personal Data
------------------------

Protection of your person privacy is an important core value of Thermaltake. We will not provide your personal data to any third party who is not related to the services of this Website, unless your consent is obtained or the laws grant us to do that. You shall keep your web password and information about your member account in a proper way and shall not release personal data (especially web password) to any person. Please remember to log off your account after completely using every service provided by our Website and remember to close the browser window if you are sharing a computer with others or using a public computer.

* It will be considered that we have clearly informed the following when members provide personal data to us.
    
* Name of Collector: Thermaltake (address: 5F, 185, Ti-Ding Avenue Sec. 2, Nei-Hu District, Taipei City, Taiwan. Tel: 886-87975788, email:[info@thermaltake.com](mailto:info@thermaltake.com)
    
* Legal basis that we use your personal data
    
    * Consent: You agree that we may use your personal data for one or several particular purposes.
    * Performance of Agreement: We collect and deal with your personal data for the purpose of entering agreement with you or providing services listed in the agreement.
    * Legal Duty: We may use your personal data to do our legal duties.
    
* The type, purpose, territory, target, method and custody period of the personal data we collected are elaborated as follows: 
    
    |     |     |     |     |     |
    | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
    | Category of Personal Data | Purpose of Collection | Territory Used | Target and Method used | Period for Custody |
    | Name | ■ performance of agreement or provision of services   <br>■ individual identification   <br>■ related promotion for distribution or advertisement   <br>■ For products or services development purposes | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer services after sale, management for website or members, etc.)   <br>■ To provide promotion and advisement materials or inform you for joining promotion activities.   <br>■ To check and confirm your identity when you contact us.   <br>■ To conduct related investigation, statistical or research/analysis for our products or services. | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purpose or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Address | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ For promotion purposes like distribution or advertisement   <br>■ For products or services development purpose | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer after sale services, management for websites or members, etc.)   <br>■ To provide promotion and advisement materials or inform you for joining promotion activities.   <br>■ To conduct related investigation, statistical or research/analysis for our products or services | ■ During a certain period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected them for, time for dealing with the data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purpose or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Date of Birth | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ individual identification   <br>■ For promotion purpose like distribution or advertisement   <br>■ For products or services development purposes | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer services after sale, management for website or members, etc.)   <br>■ To check and confirm your identity when you contact us.   <br>■ To conduct related investigation, statistical or research/analysis for our products or services | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Contact Phone Number | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ individual identification   <br>■ For promotion purpose like distribution or advertisement | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer after sale services, management for website or members, etc.)   <br>■ To provide promotion and advisement materials or inform you for joining promotion activities.   <br>■ To check and confirm your identity when you contact us. | ■ During a certain period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purposes we collected them for , time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | E-mail Address | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ For promotion purposes like distribution or advertisement | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer after sale services, management for website or members, etc.)   <br>■ To provide promotion and advisement materials or inform you for joining promotion activities. | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | ID Number (or Passport Number) | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ individual identification   <br>■ For promotion purposes like distribution or advertisement | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, after sale customer services, management for website or members, etc.)   <br>■ To check and confirm your identity when you contact us. | ■ During a certain period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Account information regarding credit card or financial organization | ■ To perform agreement or provide service | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use for service provision purpose | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any activities that are required to provide your electronic business or perform agreement (such as deliver goods, make payment, inquiry of progress, order cancellation, customer after sale services, management for website or members, etc.) | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purposes we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Internet IP Address | ■ To perform agreement or provide service   <br>■ For products or services development purpose | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ Any necessary activities to provide you electronic business services or perform the agreement (such as convert to proper currency based on your location)   <br>■ To conduct related investigation, statistical or research/analysis for our products or services | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purpose we collected, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    | Website Browser Record   <br>(Google Analytics service) | ■ For promotion purposes like distribution or advertisement   <br>■ For products or services development purposes | ■ Taiwan, or the country where our subsidiary’s business office is located, or any territory that is required to use it for service provision purposes | ■ The targets are Thermaltake and its relevant subsidiaries   <br>■ To conduct related investigation, statistical or research/analysis for our products or services | ■ During a period, we will keep relevant information subject to the purposes we collected them for, time for dealing with data, starting from your provision of personal data, to the time point below.   <br>(1) termination of the collection purposes or service listed on the left column; or   <br>(2) You expressly asked us to delete. |
    
* **Members’ rights on personal information**   
    As the owner of the personal data we collected, you are entitled to claim the following rights in accordance with the personal data protection act or the EU GDPR
    
    * Inquires or is asking for a review
    * Asking for copies
    * Asking for supplement or correction
    * Asking for ceasing collection, dealing with, or use
    * Asking for deletion
    * Asking for use detail for personal data
    * Refusing for promotion or restriction of personal data use method
    * Asking for taking out information
    * Cancelation of license consent at any time (however, our use of the personal data you provided is legitimate before you cancel your consent)
    * You are entitled to complain to the data protection and monitoring organization of the country you are located in, provided that we did not answer your inquires.
    
* You may contact to our customer service center for application if you are willing to enforce your rights stated above and we will reply to you as soon as possible. Please be informed that you have to provide your personal data to us for identification for the purpose of protection of your rights and interests. Contact Information of Thermaltake Customer Service Center Address: 5F, 185, Ti-Ding Avenue Sec. 2, Nei-Hu District, Taipei City, Taiwan Tel: 886-8797-5788 ；email： [info@thermaltake.com](mailto:info@thermaltake.com)
    
* Please note that you may not enjoy our full services or cannot use specific services if you refuse to provide us with the necessary information for registering as a member

Cookie
------

To enhance your use, the relevant Website of Thermaltake will use cookie technologies to facilitate the services you require. A cookie is a technology that the Web server uses to communicate with your browser. It may randomly store strings in your computer to identify different users. If you turn off the cookies, you may not be able to successfully access the network station or use related features such as the situation.

Google Analytics
----------------

We will use Google Analytics services in our websites. Google Analytics uses so-called cookies as explained further under the heading “Cookies and similar tracking technology” above. The information generated by the cookies about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. Further information about Google’s privacy policy may be obtained from[http://www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).   
  
You can prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) from being passed on to Google, and the processing of these data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link:[https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).   
  
You can also prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. An opt-out cookie will be set to prevent your data from being collected on future visits to this site: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

Revision of Privacy Protection Policies
---------------------------------------

We may from time to time revise the privacy protection policies in accordance with the change of marketing and environment or the requirement of laws. Our group will announce the revision on our Website if there is an amendment. Members may check our most updated privacy protection policies that we have announced. Members may contact us via e-mail ( [info@thermaltake.com](mailto:info@thermaltake.com)) should you have any inquiries about privacy statements in our Website or any matters regarding personal information. 

#### Contact Us

#### Support

#### Community

#### Company

#### LCGS Store

#### Language

* Your Location： Global
* **Select Store**
    
    [Global](javascript:void(0) "Global")

Sign Up for Our Newsletter:

Subscribe

Copyright © 2019 Thermaltake Technology Co., Ltd. All Rights Reserved.

[](javascript:void(0) "Go to Top")

We have detected a different Store for You, According to your country.

Shopping From **United States** ? Looking for **USA** Store.

IMPORTANT NOTICE OF PRIVACY POLICY

[Accept](javascript:cookieNoticeAccept();) [Close](javascript:cookieClose();) [More](https://www.thermaltake.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode)

Cookie Settings
